https://paraglide.co.uk/privacy.html

About Us
Welcome to our Store!
We have a wide range of Paragliding and Paramotoring equipment available in our store
Customer Service
Communication
With the nature of our business always dictated by the weather, we do not keep regular office hours. Answering calls when we are teaching is disruptive and so the best thing to do to get us is send a text SMS meassage to 07970421373 or join our telegram groups and we will get back to you when safe to do so
Ask the experts
There is an enormous wealth of expertise amongst our instructors - far better advice than you will find on Youtube or forums, its well worth listening to experts who have been in the sport 30 years!
Information
Customer Service
About Us
Log In
Create Account
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Categories
EQUIPMENT SHOPParagliding Courses South WalesParagliding Tandem FlightsParagliding Courses AbroadParamotor CoursesGift Certificates
Learning to Paraglide
Learning to Paramotor
Tandem Paragliding flights Wales
Forms
Photo gallery
Axis paragliding links
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Axis Training will not breach the confidence of any customer. We will not disclose your details to any other Parties. We only keep the details you supply to us to enable us to fulfil the tasks you have asked of us which may include sending information periodically. You can find what details we have by logging onto our website through the on-line shop area or simply by contacting us.
Information Collection and Use
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalised shopping experience. We will share the data we collect with our Merchant Services supplier solely for the purpose of fulfilling your order. During the site use , registration or ordering process we collect some or all of the following information: information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation
- Your name and address
- Your contact telephone numbers (to enable us to contact you in the event of a query)
- Your e-mail address
- For credit / debit card purchases your card details details are held by our Merchant Services, not by us.
We will confirm your personal details on our acknowledgement of order. If you have registered you may check, amend or remove your personal details by clicking the login button. If you are not registered you may check, amend or remove your personal details by contacting us via the contact page, e-mailing us, writing to us or calling 01873 850111. By registering or ordering through our website you consent to the collection and processing of your personal details by us.
Registration and Newsletter
Registration is required to use our website for purchasing. To speed up future purchases and avoid retyping your details you may register with us and we will store your personal details securely with access protected by a Username and password. We send all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify Username and password. When registering you may opt to receive periodic newsletters, marketing information, special offers and website updates from us. If you wish to receive these without ordering please register anyway. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or any other information you may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us via the contact page, e-mailing us, writing to us or calling 01873 850111
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data containing information about the user which may be stored on the user's hard drive. We do not use persistent cookies which are stored on your computer, but we do use temporary 'per session' cookies for tracking your searches, shopping basket items and checkout details. If you have your per session cookies turned off or have set the highest level of security in your browser settings you may be unable to purchase items from our site.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the website, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to / from 3rd party websites
We are not responsible for and accept no liability for the content or privacy practices of any linked website which is not owned and maintained by us. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.
Back
Reviews  [more]
We just wanted to say a very big thank you for the tandem...
Copyright © 2020 Axis Training.
Powered by Zen Cart.
Mobile Friendly Zen cart templates by Picaflor Azul.
Site Map
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
